There's a little bit of controversy right now. There's an accusation that the Arkansas Education
Department removed credit for controversial AP African American Studies course. Let me just read
to you what the NAACP said and let you respond. They said the Arkansas State Conference of the
NAACP is appalled at the recent decision of Arkansas Department of Education to make a
hasteful decision at the final hour to do away with AP African American Studies. Is that really
what happened there? Absolutely not. And one of the things that we have talked about so much,
and Dana, I think the point that you made a minute ago about the staggering numbers that we're seeing
across this country, we've got to get back to the basics of teaching math, of teaching reading,
writing, and American history. And we cannot perpetuate a lie to our students and push this
propaganda leftist agenda, teaching our kids to hate America and hate one another. It's one of
the reasons that we put into law banning things like indoctrination and CRT. We want our kids to
receive a quality education. We want to make sure that every student has access to it and a pathway
to prosperity. And that's exactly what we're doing here in the state of Arkansas.